🎶
Tenemos fainters to dust
You know the rules and so far
After commitments, follow the king of the kingdom
You won't get this wrong, any other guy
I just wanna tell you how I feel
I ain't gotta make you understand
Never gonna give you home
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, you just let you
Never gonna make you cry
I'm gonna gonna shake you back
Never gonna tell you how I feel
And that you
We know each other
For so long
Your thoughts be naked, man
Your just shy to say
It's like you saw we've walked over
Spin, go, no
We know the game I'm gonna play
And if you ask me how I feel
Don't tell me you're too
Not to see, never gonna give you home
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, you just let you
Never gonna make you cry
I'm gonna shake you back
Never gonna tell you how I feel
And that you
Never gonna give you home
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around
Never gonna run around it
You just let you
Never gonna make you cry
We know each other
Never gonna give you home
We've known each other for so long
Your heart's been aching us
Your just has to say it
If it's happening for the last been going on
We know the game and we're gonna play it
I just wanna tell you how I feel it
Gotta make you understand
Never gonna give you out
Gonna let you down
Gonna wanna run and you just do
Gonna make you proud
Gonna say it goodbye
Gonna wanna tell you how I feel it
Gotta make you understand
Gonna wanna run and you just do
Gonna make you proud
Gonna say it goodbye
It break you
Gonna give you out
Gonna let you down
Gonna wanna run and you just do
Gonna make you proud
Gonna say it goodbye